

NGUYEN QUANG THANH



I want to get more experience, challenge myself in many job positions and develop my own skills. With the spirit of inquisitive and highly adaptable to the environment, I believe that I will easily take on this position in a short time.

Work experience

Jun 2021 - Aug 2021

Data Scientist Interns

TMA SOLUTIONS BINH DINH

- Report the training process to the mentor
- Data visualization, data analysis of customer buying behavior
- -Tools: Python, Tableau.

Jan 2022 - May 2022

Front-end Interns

BYS Da Nang

- Report the training process to the mentor
- Design mockup
- Build website interface
- Tools: Html, Css, Javascript, Bootstrap, Figma, Visio



Date of birth

May 4, 2000



0848787728



Email

nqthanh452@gmail.com



Waheita

https://www.linkedin.com/in/thanhnguyez/



Address

Da Nang Vietnam



Gender

Male



Education

DANANG UNIVERSITY OF ECONOMICS | FROM 2018 - 2022

Major: Management information systems



Programming language & Tools

ReactJS:

Basic

SQL:

Basic

Figma, Visio:

Basic



Certifications

2022

TOEIC 510